I called my first dry bar comedy special
manly girly
man because although I'm not a manly man
I'm not a girly man either I'm right in
the middle I'm what you might call a
manly girly
man whenever one of my manly man friends
says hey Jeff what would you rather have
bro a Dodge Challenger Hellcat or a
Shelby Mustang 5.0 I'm like I don't care
bro whichever one has eight cylinders
and comes in purple
whenever one of my manly man friends
says hey Jeff who rocks harder bro
Aerosmith or Metallica I'm like
Aerosmith bro because those guys are
survivors and Dude Looks Like A Lady is
my
J if there any manly men here tonight
and we have a few you sir are a manly
man you sir a manly man you sir on the
waiting list
how do you like that sir you just got
roasted by Keith Urban
sister but if there are any manly men
here tonight who are wondering if you
two like me May me a manly girly man
there's a way you can tell so with
apologies to one of my favorite
comedians Jeff you might be a redneck if
[Music]
Foxworthy if you you ever walked into a
butcher shop and asked for pumpkin spice
beef jerky you might be a manly girly
man if you've ever watched a
professional wrestler pum an opponent
with a folding chair and thought nice
Cape you might be a manly girly
man if you've ever watched a John Wick
movie with keano Reeves and wish there
had been more scenes with the dog you
might be am manly girly
man if a woman asks you if you have
protection and you whip out a tube of
sun block you might be a manly girlly
[Applause]
man if the only thing you've ever made
with your own two hands is gluten-free
banana nut bread sir you might be a
manly girlly
man if you carry an allen wrench on your
keychain just in case you make an imp by
Ikea you might be a manly girlly
man if you've ever thought of becoming a
long shoreman just so you can get
discounts at Pier One you might be a
manly girly
man and if you're sitting there thinking
but Jeff didn't Pier One go out of
business over a year ago then you are
definitely a manly girly man
[Applause]
and finally if you've ever turned three
albums worth of funny at formic on
liners into a multi-million doll
entertainment Empire you might be
smarter than a fifth grader
[Applause]